creativejobscentral.com 2019-04-26

# Privacy Policy | CreativeJobsCentral

We are highly sensitive to the privacy interests of consumers and believe that the protection of those interests is one of its most significant responsibilities. Thus, we have adopted the following Privacy Policy applicable to information about consumers that it acquires in the course of its business:

###  **Acquisition of Information**

We do not acquire any more information about consumers than is required by law or is otherwise necessary to provide a high level of service efficiently and securely.  

###  **Our Employees and Privacy**

We train all of our employees about the importance of privacy. We give access to information about consumers only to those employees who require it to perform their jobs.  

###  **Security Measures**

We make access to privacy-sensitive information subject to rigorous procedural and technological controls, consistent with legal requirements and the demands of customer's service.

The company has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. These measures include a firewall to prevent unauthorized access to our systems and maintenance of registration information in a secure database.

We do our best to provide secure transmission of information between your computer and our servers. However, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us over The Internet and we accept no liability for any unintentional disclosure.

###  **Disclosure to Third Parties**

We will provide individually-identifiable information about consumers to third parties only if we are compelled to do so by order of a duly-empowered governmental authority, we have the express permission of the consumer, or it is necessary to process transactions and provide our services.  

###  **Privacy and Our Business Partners**

When we make our technology or services available to business partners, we will not share with them any more consumer information then is necessary, and we will make every reasonable effort to assure, that they use our technology and services in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.

###  Use of Personal Information.

###  Technical Information

We may collect IP address for diagnostics, aggregated demographic/geographic statistics (personal IP information will never be shared with third parties)

Cookies for ease of site usage and some statistical purposes (Data collected from cookies will never be shared with third parties)

Uploading your contacts to CreativeJobsCentral

We will never store or keep your login information. We will never sell, rent, or give access to your contact lists. We will only access your contact lists with your explicit consent.

###  Collecting and Sharing Job Information

We may use demographic information about a job posting, including location, hiring firm, and other information, for statistical and development purposes.

We will never share information that you post on the website with any third party without your explicit consent. It is a Terms and Conditions violation for a member to copy any piece of Job Information from CreativeJobsCentral. Any member found doing so is immediately terminated. All correspondence between you and prospective candidates done through the website is strictly confidential.

After registration, CreativeJobsCentral may contact you via email with periodic notifications about network updates, messages, and new features and services.

We may transfer personal information of our users to a third party as part of the acquisition of CreativeJobsCentral or its assets. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to this Privacy Policy.

###  Sharing Information with Third Parties.

We suggest that you share certain personal information with third parties for special contests and promotions, (we will never share personal information for these purposes without your explicit consent). Whether you choose to do this is, and will remain, your choice.

###  Links to other websites.

CreativeJobsCentral may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We may also link to websites that feature Company trademarks and names along with trademarks and names of other companies. You should look at the privacy policy on that website, as that website may not be under CreativeJobsCentral's control.

We are not responsible for privacy practices found on other websites accessed through CreativeJobsCentral.

###  Security Measures.

The company has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. These measures include a firewall to prevent unauthorized access to our systems and maintenance of registration information in a secure database.

We do our best to provide secure transmission of information between your computer and our servers. However, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us over The Internet and we accept no liability for any unintentional disclosure.

###  User Agreement.

As a user of CreativeJobsCentral you will have access to other users' personal information. You agree to use this information solely for recruiting purposes. The company and its users shall not tolerate spam of any kind. Accounts suspected of causing spam will be deactivated immediately. Please feel free to report any misuse of CreativeJobsCentral by contacting us at support@CreativeJobsCentral.com.

Your use of the company web sites, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this Privacy Policy and the Company's Terms and Conditions. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changes on this page. Please check the revision date at the bottom of this page to determine if the statement has been modified since you last reviewed it. Your continued use of any portion of the company web sites following posting of the updated Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.
